http://www.wvsymphony.org/privacy-policy

Support
Make A Gift Today!
Become a Music Maker!
Press Releases
Concerts & Tickets/Browse Concerts & EventsTicketing InformationLive Stream FAQSubscriptions
Support/Make A Gift Today!Become a Music Maker!Giving TuesdaySponsorsPlanned GivingGrants, Funds & FoundationsIndividual Donors
Education/Student OpportunitiesDunphy ScholarshipString Education ProgramYoung People's ConcertsVaughan FellowshipWVSO KIDS
About/Maestro Loh & MusiciansBoard & StaffMission & HistoryDiversity, Equity, & InclusionSymphony ChorusAuditions 2020
Privacy Policy
Concerts & Tickets/Browse Concerts & EventsTicketing InformationLive Stream FAQSubscriptions
Support/Make A Gift Today!Become a Music Maker!Giving TuesdaySponsorsPlanned GivingGrants, Funds & FoundationsIndividual Donors
Education/Student OpportunitiesDunphy ScholarshipString Education ProgramYoung People's ConcertsVaughan FellowshipWVSO KIDS
About/Maestro Loh & MusiciansBoard & StaffMission & HistoryDiversity, Equity, & InclusionSymphony ChorusAuditions 2020
SHOP/
Coronavirus (COVID-19) Impact/
Media Room/Watch & ListenBehind the ScorePress Releases
PRIVACY POLICYThe West Virginia Symphony Orchestra is committed to honoring your privacy and to protecting the integrity of our website. We want to ensure that your visits to our site are free of unwelcome intrusions. Therefore we will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer to give to us. We will never willfully disclose your personal information to any third parties without your prior consent.The circumstances under which you may be given the opportunity to provide personal information include registering for contests, subscribing to e-mail newsletters, and purchasing tickets and CDs via our secure server.We reserve the right to release aggregate, anonymous demographic information supplied by visitors to third parties. We may also disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or to protect against the misuse of our website or against other violations of our rights or the rights of our users or the public.We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to help protect the information we gather online in accordance with this privacy policy.With your prior permission, New World will send you messages from time to time on behalf of a third party. In all cases, the message we send will be clearly identified as coming to you from the New World Symphony. With each e-mail, you will be given an opportunity to opt out from receiving such future messages by utilizing an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each e-mail message.If you have any concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us by clicking here.This policy, which is effective as of May 1, 2016, has been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving. This policy is therefore subject to change. If the changes represent a material departure from our current practices, they will be posted on this page prior to taking effect.WHAT ARE COOKIES?A “cookie” is a small file containing non-personal information that we save on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited. We use cookies to help us determine how many people visit our site, which of our web pages they stop at and how long they stay there. This information helps us know which web features are useful, and which might need improvement. For administrative purposes, we collect IP addresses, the automatic number assigned to your computer when you surf the Web. The IP address allows us to count the total number of “hits” on our sites. However, your IP address and cookie are not connected to any personally identifiable or online contact information, so you remain anonymous. West Virginia Symphony Orchestra reserves the right to send cookies associated with our website to your computer. In addition, we will not release cookie information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without your consent. Our website also contains links to other sites not maintained by us that will have their own privacy policies over which we have no control. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with a website’s privacy policy before you volunteer personal information.
Concerts & Tickets/Browse Concerts & EventsTicketing InformationLive Stream FAQSubscriptions
Support/Make A Gift Today!Become a Music Maker!Giving TuesdaySponsorsPlanned GivingGrants, Funds & FoundationsIndividual Donors
Education/Student OpportunitiesDunphy ScholarshipString Education ProgramYoung People's ConcertsVaughan FellowshipWVSO KIDS
About/Maestro Loh & MusiciansBoard & StaffMission & HistoryDiversity, Equity, & InclusionSymphony ChorusAuditions 2020
SHOP/
Coronavirus (COVID-19) Impact/
Media Room/Watch & ListenBehind the ScorePress Releases
West Virginia Symphony Orchestra
The West Virginia Symphony Orchestra is West Virginia’s premier performing arts organization, presenting classical, pops, and chamber-music concerts annually throughout the Mountain State. Currently in its 78th season, the WVSO is a proud member of the community and enriches the region by providing affordable, high-quality concerts, collaborations with West Virginia arts organizations and a nationally award-winning education program.
Privacy Policy   Contact us"Tales from West Virginia Hills" CDLike. Friend. Follow.
4700 MacCorkle Avenue SE, Suite 101 Charleston, WV 25304Phone 304.957.WVSO (9876)SEND US EMAIL
Email Address
Sign me up
Thank you!
